A Guide to the Papers of Rear Admiral Walter C. Ansel, 1924-1974
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Documents of the German Military during World War II
  - Supreme commander in Chief of the German Navy (Ob.d.M)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 23 Oct. 1939 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 8 Nov. 1939 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 10 Nov. 1939 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 22 Nov. 1939 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 8 Dec. 1939 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Ob.d.M. memo to O.K.W., 11 Dec. 1939 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 12 Dec. 1939 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 16 Dec. 1939 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 30 Dec. 1939 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 26 Jan. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 20 Feb. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 23 Feb. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 9 Mar. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 26 Mar. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 29 Mar. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 10 Apr. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 14 Apr. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 22 Apr. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 26 Apr. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 29 Apr. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Ob.d.M. memo to O.K.W., 6 May 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 7 May 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 21 May 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 22 May 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Ob.d.M. report on Operation Wessunbung, 22 May 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Ob.d.M. memo to all military branches, 23 May 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 26 May 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 29 May 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 4 Jun. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Ob.d.M. report on ship positions, 11 Jun. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Ob.d.M. report on transportation of troops and position of landing craft, 15 Jun. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 20 Jun. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Ob.d.M. memo to the Supreme Naval Command West, 29 Jun. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Ob.d.M. report on preparations of material for Operation Sea Lion, 6 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Ob.d.M. proposals to invade England, 7 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 11 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Ob.d.M. Naval War Staff memo to the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 16 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Ob.d.M. memo to other military branches, 20 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Ob.d.M. report on cost, 21 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Ob.d.M. memo to other military branches about the war effort, 22 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Ob.d.M. memo to other military branches, 26 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Ob.d.M. report on Operation Sea Lion, 30 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Ob.d.M. memo to O.K.L. and O.K.W., 1 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Ob.d.M., Naval War Staff report to the Fuehrer, 13 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Ob.d.M. report on Sea Lion, 16 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Ob.d.M. memo to the Supreme Naval Group Commanders West and North, 20 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Ob.d.M. memo to O.K.H., 22 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 7 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Ob.d.M. memo to Generaladmiral Albecht, 17 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Ob.d.M. memo to Generaladmiral Albecht, 25 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 14 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Ob.d.M. memo to O.K.H., 6 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Ob.d.M. report on Vermark, 9 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Ob.d.M. memo to Generaladmiral Albecht, 11 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 27 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Ob.d.M. memo to the Naval War Staff, 8 Feb. 1940 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Ob.d.M. material with no date (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Supreme Command of the German Navy (O.K.M. - Kriegsmarine)
    - O.K.M. report on Sea Lion, 5 Jun. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 1)
    - O.K.M. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, 7 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 2)
    - O.K.M. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, 15 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 3)
    - O.K.M. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, 16 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 4)
    - O.K.M. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, 19 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 5)
    - O.K.M. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, 20 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 6)
    - O.K.M. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, 22 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 7)
    - O.K.M. report on supplies on the EDMEN, 23 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 8)
    - O.K.M. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, 24 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 9)
    - O.K.M. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, 25 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 10)
    - O.K.M. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, 26 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 11)
    - O.K.M. to Naval Port Commanders, 27 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 12)
    - O.K.M. report on preparation of landing craft, 30 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 13)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding France, 31 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 14)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval West, 1 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 15)
    - O.K.M. memo to other Naval Branches, 2 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 16)
    - O.K.M. memo to other Naval Branches, 5 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 17)
    - O.K.M. memo to other Naval Branches, 6 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 18)
    - O.K.M. memo to other Naval Branches, 7 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 19)
    - O.K.M. memos to Naval Port Commanders, Supreme Naval Group West, and Admiral Commanding France, 8 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 20)
    - O.K.M. memo to other Naval Branches, 10 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 21)
    - O.K.M. memo to Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff, 12 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 22)
    - O.K.M. memo to Naval Port Commander Wilhelmshaven and to the Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group West, 14 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 23)
    - O.K.M. report on various landing craft and location, 15 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 24)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group West, 16 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 25)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group West and his departments, 18 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 26)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding France, Admiral Commanding the Netherlands, Supreme Naval Group West, etc., 22 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 27)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group West and Port Commanders, 23 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 28)
    - O.K.M. memo to Supreme Naval Group West, Naval Port Commanders, Supreme Naval Group Command North, etc., 26 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 29)
    - O.K.M. memo to Naval Station North Sea, Naval Station East Sea, Chief of Staff West, and Quartermaster General of the Army, 27 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 30)
    - O.K.M. memo to Supreme Naval Command Groups West and North, and Naval Station East (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 31)
    - O.K.M. memo to O.K.H. and several Naval Departments, 29 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 32)
    - O.K.M. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, 30 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 33)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding France, and other Naval Departments, 3 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 34)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding France, 4 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 35)
    - O.K.M. memo to O.K.W. and other Naval Departments, 5 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 36)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding France, Supreme Naval Group Commands West and North, etc., 6 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 37)
    - O.K.M. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West and other Naval Stations, 7 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 38)
    - O.K.M. memo to Naval Officer Commanding Port Ostende, 8 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 39)
    - O.K.M. memo to Supreme Naval Group Commands West and North, 9 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 40)
    - O.K.M. memo to the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 10 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 41)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 13 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 42)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 14 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 43)
    - O.K.M. memo to Naval Port Command Wihelmshaven, 19 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 44)
    - O.K.M. memo to Naval Port Command Antwerpen, 25 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 45)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 24 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 46)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West and Other Naval Departments, 31 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 47)
    - O.K.M. memo to Naval Port Commanders, 5 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 48)
    - O.K.M. memo to all Naval Departments, 7 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 49)
    - O.K.M. report on meeting between Ob.d.M. and the Fuehrer, 3 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 50)
    - O.K.M. from the special staff of B.S.W., 14 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 51)
    - O.K.M. memo to organization Naval Officer of Sea Lion, 21 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 52)
    - O.K.M. memo to the Inspector of Naval Artillery, 13 Jan. 1941 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 53)
    - O.K.M. memo to the Central Staff of the Armed Forces High Command, and other Military Branches, 16 Jan. 1941 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 54)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding France and other Naval Departments, 20 Jan. 1941 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 55)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 11 Mar. 1941 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 56)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding the Netherlands, 25 Mar. 1941 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 57)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding Antwerp, 30 Mar. 1940 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 58)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding all Naval Ports, 3 May 1941 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 59)
    - O.K.M. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West (no date) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 60)
    - O.K.M. report on English and American Naval Strength (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Naval War Staff (Skl. - Kriegsmarine)
    - Skl. message to Kapitan zur See Lokye, 16 May 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Skl. message to Kapitan zur See Lokye, 14 Jun. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Skl. memo to O.K.H. and O.K.L. central staffs, 8 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Skl. message to Kapitan zur See Lokye, 11 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Skl. report on the mining of English Channel, 17 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Skl. message to Kapitan zur See Lokye, 19 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Skl. memo to Field Transport Staff, Naval Station North Sea, Supreme Naval Group Command West, and Naval Port Command Wilhelmshaven, 22 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Skl. memo to O.K.L.'s central staff, 24 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Skl. memo to Operations Department of the Naval War Staff, 29 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, Admiral Commanding France, Naval Command West, etc., 3 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Skl. memo to O.K.W., O.K.L., O.K.H., and Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 4 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Chief of Skl.'s report to the Chief of Staff of the Army General Staff, 7 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Skl. report Intelligence reports on the English Defense Forces, 9 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Chief of Skl.'s report on his meeting with the Chief of Staff to the Army General Staff, 12 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Chief of Skl.'s memo to O.K.W., 18 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, Admiral Commanding the Netherlands, Admiral Commanding Naval Station North Sea, 19 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, Admiral Commanding the Netherlands, Admiral Commanding Naval Station North Sea, 20 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, Admiral Commanding the Netherlands, Admiral Commanding Naval Station North Sea, 21 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, Admiral Commanding the Netherlands, Admiral Commanding Naval Station North Sea, 22 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, Admiral Commanding the Netherlands, Admiral Commanding Naval Station North Sea, 24 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, 25 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding France, Supreme Naval Group Command West, Admiral Commanding the Netherlands, Channel Coastal Defense, and Admiral Commanding the North Sea, 26-27 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding France, Naval Officers Commanding the Naval Ports Ostende, Antwerp, and Rotterdam, 28 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command North, 29 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command's West and North, Admiral Commanding France, Chief of Staff to the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 30 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Skl. memo to O.K.M., 31 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, 2 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Skl. memo to O.K.H., Naval Port Commanders in the West, and the Operations Department of the Naval War Staff, 4 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Skl. memo to the Supreme Naval Group Command West and other departments, 5 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff memo to the Operations Department of the Naval War Staff, 6 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Skl. memo to the Supreme Naval Group Command North, Naval Port Command Wilhelmshaven, Kiel, and the Commanding Officer of the Bismarck, 7 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Skl. memo to the Supreme Naval Group Command's North and East Sea, and Naval Port Command Kiel, 12 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Skl. report on the meeting between Ob.d.M. and the Fuehrer, 14 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff memo to the Operations Department of the Naval War Staff, 15 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Skl. memo to the Supreme Naval Group Command's West and North, and the Admiral Commanding France, 17 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Skl. memo to the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 20 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Skl. report on the transportation fleet, 21 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff report on the meeting with the Fuehrer, 23 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff memo to the Operations Department of the Naval War Staff, 24 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Skl. report on the meeting between the Ob.d.M. and the Fuehrer, 26 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Skl. report on the transportation fleet, 28 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Skl. memo to the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 2 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Skl. report on the meeting between Ob.d.M. and the Fuehrer, 14 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West and the Admiral Commanding France, 23 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Skl. report to the Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff (out of Official War Record), 11 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Skl. report on the meeting between Ob.d.M., and the Fuehrer, 14 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Skl. memo to O.K.H., 21 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Skl. report on the meeting between Ob.d.M. and the Fuhrer, 27 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Skl. report on the meeting between O.K.W. and the Fuehrer, 9 Jan. 1941 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Skl. memo to the Supreme Naval Group Command's West and North, and Admiral Commanding France (no date) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Skl. Diagrams, Maps, and charts, 5 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 51)
    - 1/Skl. memo to O.K.H. and the Chief of Staff of the Army General Staff, 8 Jan. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 1/Skl. report on the meeting between Ob.d.M. and the Fuehrer, 14 Apr. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 2)
    - 1/Skl. report on the mine development and minesweeping in the English Channel, 17 Jun. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 3)
    - 1/Skl. memo to naval branches about Sea Lion, 20 Jun. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 4)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Ob.d.M, 6 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 5)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Chief of Staff's of the Army General Staff and the Airforce General Staff, 9 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 6)
    - 1/Skl. memo to the Naval Liason officer assigned to the Army General Staff, 12 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 7)
    - 1/Skl. memo to the Naval Liason officer assigned to the Army General Staff, 14 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 8)
    - 1/Skl. memo to naval departments PA and WEHR, 15 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 1/Skl. memo to naval departments A, A II, A VI, and IOPE, 17 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 10)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Chief of A VI and K III M, 18 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 11)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West, Naval Departments A, MPA, A Ma, etc., 19 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 12)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command's West and East, Admiral Commanding the Fleet, Admirals Commanding France and Norway, 20 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 13)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Admirals Commanding France and Northern France, 21 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 14)
    - 1/Skl. memo to O.K.W., 22 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 15)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Naval Commands of English Channel and Netherlands, memo to O.K.W., O.K.H., O.K.L., 23 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 16)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Commands West and East, Admiral Commanding Norway, and Naval Department A., 24 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 17)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding Netherlands, O.K.W., O.K.H., O.K.L., and other naval departments, 25 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 18)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West and O.K.H., 26 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 19)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Naval Department A VII, 29 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 20)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Naval Department M WA WI, 30 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 21)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Commands West and East, Chief of Staff to the Naval War Staff, Admrial Commanding Norway, 1 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 22)
    - 1/Skl. memo to both Army and Airforce General Staffs, 2 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 23)
    - 1/Skl. memo to naval departments A M Wa on Sea Lion, 3 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 24)
    - 1/Skl. report on Sea Lion, 5 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 25)
    - 1/Skl. memo to O.K.W. and the General Staffs of the Army and Air Force, 6 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 26)
    - 1/Skl. memo to naval departments MPA, A, A II, A III, AMA, and M-Wehr, 8 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 27)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Army General Staff and the Supreme Naval Command North, 9 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 28)
    - 1/Skl. memo to O.K.W., 10 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 29)
    - 1/Skl. memo to naval department A and Supreme Naval Group Command West, 12 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 30)
    - 1/Skl. memo to naval departments A(A II), A(A VI), M Wa, A(A VI) K(K III), 14 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 31)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West and Naval Commander West, 15 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 32)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 16 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 33)
    - 1/Skl. memo to naval departments A(A VI), M Wa, K, etc. and Supreme Naval Group Command West, 15 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 34)
    - 1/Skl. memo to naval departments A(A VI), M Wa, K, etc. and Supreme Naval Group Command West, 20 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 35)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Naval Liaison to AOK 16, lop, and Supreme Naval Group Command West, 22 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 36)
    - 1/Skl. memo to both Army and Airforce General Staffs, Supreme Naval Group Command North, 23 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 37)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Supreme Naval Group Command West and Naval Command West, 24 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 38)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Ob.d.M., Supreme Naval Group Commands North and West, and Naval Commands North and West, 25 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 39)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding France, 27 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 40)
    - 1/Skl. memo to Admiral Commanding the Supreme Naval Group Command West, 29 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 41)
    - 1/Skl. memo to both Army and Airforce General Staffs, Supreme Naval Group Command West, and Admiral commanding France, 30 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 42)